Planned Parenthood Federation of America Records (PPFA II): SERIES V. Affiliates, 1930-80 (Part 2)
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES V. AFFILIATES (PART 2)
  - Oklahoma
    - Norman
      - Reports, General, 1967 (Box 172, Folder 67)
      - Reports, Members, 1968-1971 (Box 172, Folder 68)
    - Oklahoma City
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1953
        - 1953-1972 (Box 172, Folder 69)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 172)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1960
        - 1960-1972 (Box 172, Folder 70)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 172)
      - PP Association of Oklahoma City, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1978 (Box 172, Folder 71)
      - PP Association from 1969
        - 1969-1974 (Box 172, Folder 72)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 172)
      - PP, Merger, 1971-1972 (Box 172, Folder 73)
      - PP Association, 1961-1968 (Box 172, Folder 74)
      - Reports, Clinics from 1967 (empty) (Box 172, Folder 75)
      - PP Association, Reports, General, 1960-1970 (Box 172, Folder 76)
      - PP Association, Reports, Members, 1962-1974 (Box 172, Folder 77)
      - PP Association, Publicity, 1963-1971 (Box 172, Folder 78)
      - Field Trips, 1954-1967 (Box 172, Folder 79)
    - Shawnee
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1966-1969 (Box 172, Folder 80)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 172, Folder 81)
      - PP Pottawotamia County, 1965-1969 (Box 172, Folder 82)
      - Reports, General, 1966-1969 (Box 172, Folder 83)
      - Reports, Members, 1966-1969 (Box 172, Folder 84)
    - Tulsa
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1954
        - 1954-1972 (Box 172, Folder 85)
        - 1976, 1979 (Box 172)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1960
        - 1960-1974 (Box 173, Folder 1)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 173)
      - PP Association of Tulsa, Trip Report, Andy Diaz, 1977 (Box 173, Folder 2)
      - PP Association of Oklahoma City, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1978 (Box 173, Folder 3)
      - PP of Northeastern Oklahoma, 1977-1979 (Box 173, Folder 4)
      - PP Association of Tulsa from 1969
        - 1969-1974 (Box 173, Folder 5)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 173)
      - PP, 1964-1968 (Box 173, Folder 6)
      - 1963 (Box 173, Folder 7)
      - Field Trips, 1954-1964 (Box 173, Folder 8)
      - PP Association, Reports, General, 1963-1967 (Box 173, Folder 9)
      - PP Association, Reports, Members from 1963
        - 1962-1974 (Box 173, Folder 10)
        - 1976-1978 (Box 173)
      - PP Association, Publicity, 1954-1966 (Box 173, Folder 11)
  - Oregon
    - Anti-Poverty, Correspondence, 1969 (Box 173, Folder 12)
    - Contacts from 1963
      - 1963-1974 (Box 173, Folder 13)
      - 1976 (Box 173)
    - Legal, 1958 (Box 173, Folder 14)
    - Perco, 1977-1978 (Box 173, Folder 15)
    - Migrant from 1965 1965-1969 (Box 173, Folder 16)
    - Projects, 1970 (Box 173, Folder 17)
    - Perco, Public Education Research Council Oregon
      - 1974-1977 (Box 173, Folder 18)
      - 1975-1977 (Box 173)
    - Public Health, 1963-1974 (Box 173, Folder 19)
    - Public Welfare, 1963-1969 (Box 173, Folder 20)
    - United Fund, United Community Services, 1968-1969 (Box 173, Folder 21)
    - Schools, General, 1964-1974 (Box 173, Folder 22)
    - University of Oregon, Correspondence & Miscellaneous, 1963-1971 (Box 173, Folder 23)
    - Oregon State University, Dr. Lester A. Kirkendall, Correspondence, 1959-1972 (Box 173, Folder 24)
    - Facts of Life in Oregon, 1976 (Box 173, Folder 25)
    - Corvallis
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 173, Folder 26)
        - 1977-1979 (Box 173)
      - Affiliation, PP Benton County, Correspondence from 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 173, Folder 27)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 173)
      - PP Benton County from 1970
        - 1967-1974 (Box 173, Folder 28)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 173)
      - Reports, Members from 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 173, Folder 29)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 173)
    - Eugene
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1967
        - 1967-1974 (Box 173, Folder 30)
        - 1975 (Box 173)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1966
        - 1966-1974 (Box 173, Folder 31)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 173)
      - PP Lane County from 1965
        - 1965-1974 (Box 173, Folder 32)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 173)
      - Reports, General, 1967-1971 (Box 173, Folder 33)
      - Reports, Members from 1965
        - 1966-1970 (Box 173, Folder 34)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 173)
    - Medford
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws
        - 1967-1974 (Box 173, Folder 35)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 173)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1967
        - 1967-1974 (Box 173, Folder 36)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 173)
      - PP Jackson County from 1965
        - 1965-1974 (Box 173, Folder 37)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 173)
      - Reports, General, 1965-1971 (Box 173, Folder 38)
      - Reports, Members from 1965
        - 1965-1972 (Box 173, Folder 39)
        - 1976, 1978 (Box 173)
    - Portland
      - Affiliation, PP Association, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1963
        - 1963-1972 (Box 173, Folder 40)
        - 1975, 1978 (Box 173)
      - Affiliation, PP Association, Correspondence from 1963
        - 1963-1972 (Box 173, Folder 41)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 173)
      - PP Association, Correspondence from 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 173, Folder 42)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 173)
      - PP Association, 1964-1969 (Box 173, Folder 43)
      - PP Association, 1963 (Box 173, Folder 44)
      - Meeting of Region X Council 7/26/1971 (Box 173, Folder 45)
      - Field Trips, 1961-1966 (Box 173, Folder 46)
      - Reports, Clinics, 1963-1972 (Box 173, Folder 47)
      - Reports, General, 1963-1971 (Box 173, Folder 48)
      - PP Association, Reports, Members from 1962
        - 1963-1972 (Box 173, Folder 49)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 173)
      - Public Affairs, PP Association, Inc. of Portland, 1977 (Box 173, Folder 50)
      - Publicity, 1964-1967 (Box 173, Folder 51)
    - Western Region, Reports, Field Trips, 1965-1973 (Box 173, Folder 52)
  - Pennsylvania
    - General Correspondence, 1969 (Box 173, Folder 53)
    - Anti-Poverty Program, 1965-1973 (Box 173, Folder 54)
    - Catholic Church Anti-Family Planning Campaign, 1966 (Box 173, Folder 55)
    - Comprehensive Health Care Act, 1973 (Box 173, Folder 56)
    - Contacts from 1963
      - 1962-1974 (Box 173, Folder 57)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 173)
    - Department HEW, Family Planning Regional Director from 1971
      - 1971-1974 (Box 173, Folder 58)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 173)
    - Department of Public Instruction, 1971 (Box 173, Folder 59)
    - The Family Planning Council of East Central Pennsylvania, 1973 (Box 173, Folder 60)
    - Family Planning Council of South-Central Pennsylvania (formerly Southeastern) from 1973
      - 1973 (Box 173, Folder 61)
      - 1975, 1977 (Box 173)
    - Family Planning Information Office (FPIO) from 1974
      - 1973-1974 (Box 173, Folder 62)
      - 1975-1977 (Box 173)
    - Hospitals, General Correspondence, 1963-1974 (Box 173, Folder 63)
    - Family Planning Council of Western Pennsylvania from 1974
      - 1974 (Box 173, Folder 64)
      - 1975 (Box 173)
    - Legal, Correspondence & Miscellaneous, 1927-1974 (Box 173, Folder 65)
    - Maternal Health Services of Northeastern Pennsylvania, 1975-1976 (Box 173, Folder 66)
    - Medical Societies, Correspondence, 1956-1966 (Box 173, Folder 67)
    - Migrant, 1961-1967 (Box 173, Folder 68)
    - Pennsylvania Catastrophe Loss Fund, 1978-1979 (Box 173, Folder 69)
    - Pennsylvania Family Planning Coalition, 1974 (Box 173, Folder 70)
    - Projects, 1969-1972 (Box 173, Folder 71)
    - Public Health, Correspondence from 1963
      - 1963-1974 (Box 173, Folder 72)
      - 1976 (Box 173)
    - Public Health, Clinical Laboratories, Regulations, 1974 (Box 173, Folder 73)
    - Public Health, Health Service Agencies, 1976 (Box 173, Folder 74)
    - Public Welfare, Correspondence from 1964
      - 1964-1973 (Box 173, Folder 75)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 173)
    - Public Welfare, Publicity, 1965-1966 (Box 173, Folder 76)
    - Statewide Health Coordinating Council, 1976 (Box 173, Folder 77)
    - United Fund, United Community Services, 1966-1970 (Box 173, Folder 78)
    - Schools, General from 1963
      - 1963-1974 (Box 173, Folder 79)
      - 1975, 1977 (Box 173)
    - Schools, Chatham College, 1963 (Box 173, Folder 1)
    - Schools, University of Pennsylvania, 1965-1974 (Box 173, Folder 2)
    - Schools, University of Pittsburgh from 1963-1964
      - 1964-1973 (Box 173, Folder 3)
      - 1976 (Box 173)
    - Hoover-Perlman, 1963?-1965 (Box 173, Folder 4)
    - Schools, University of Pittsburgh, Hoover-Perlman Study, 1963-1965 (Box 173, Folder 5)
    - PP League of Northeastern Pennsylvania, 1976-1980 (Box 173, Folder 6)
    - Pennsylvania Conference of Affiliates from 1973
      - 1973-1974 (Box 173, Folder 7)
      - 1975 (Box 173)
    - Planned Parenthood Affiliates of Pennsylvania, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1979 (Box 173, Folder 8)
    - Affiliation, PP Pennsylvania Affiliates from 1974
      - 1974 (Box 173, Folder 9)
      - 1976 (Box 173)
    - PP Pennsylvania Affiliates from 1974
      - 1974 (Box 174, Folder 10)
      - 1975-1979 (Box 174)
    - Harrisburg, Family Planning Information Office from 1978
      - 1973-1974 (Box 174, Folder 11)
      - 1978 (Box 174)
    - Allentown
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1969
        - 1969-1972 (Box 174, Folder 12)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 174)
      - Affiliation, Correspondence from 1969
        - 1969-1973 (Box 174, Folder 13)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 174)
      - PP Association of Lehigh County, Trip Report, Andy Diaz, 1977 (Box 174, Folder 14)
      - PP of Lehigh County from 1969
        - 1968-1974 (Box 174, Folder 15)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 174)
      - Reports, Members, 1971-1972 (Box 174, Folder 16)
      - Field Visit, 1973 (Box 174, Folder 17)
    - Bucks County
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1965
        - 1964-1972 (Box 174, Folder 18)
        - 1975, 1978 (Box 174)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1964
        - 1964-1972 (Box 174, Folder 19)
        - 1975-1981 (Box 174)
      - PP, 1963-1970 (Box 174, Folder 20)
    - Bristol
      - PP Bucks County from 1971
        - 1971-1974 (Box 174, Folder 21)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 174)
      - Field Visits, 1973 (Box 174, Folder 22)
    - Bucks County
      - PP, Reports, General, 1963-1972 (Box 174, Folder 23)
      - PP, Reports, Members, 1964-1974 (Box 174, Folder 24)
      - PP, Publicity, 1964-1971 (Box 174, Folder 25)
    - Easton
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1950
        - 1950-1973 (Box 174, Folder 26)
        - 1976, 1980 (Box 174)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1957
        - 1957-1974 (Box 174, Folder 27)
        - 1976-1980 (Box 174)
      - Field Trips, 1957-1961 (Box 174, Folder 28)
      - PP from 1963
        - 1963-1974 (Box 174, Folder 29)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 174)
      - PP, Reports, Members, 1961-1971 (Box 174, Folder 30)
    - East Stroudsburg
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1947
        - 1947-1974 (Box 174, Folder 31)
        - 1977, 1980 (Box 174)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1957
        - 1957-1974 (Box 174, Folder 32)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 174)
      - Monroe County PP Association, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1978-1979 (Box 174, Folder 33)
      - PP from 1963
        - 1963-1974 (Box 174, Folder 34)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 174)
      - Field Visits, 1974 (Box 174, Folder 35)
      - Field Trips, 1957-1964 (Box 174, Folder 36)
      - Reports, Clinics, 1959-1964 (Box 174, Folder 37)
      - Reports, General, 1958-1966 (Box 174, Folder 38)
      - PP, Reports, Members, 1958-1972 (Box 174, Folder 39)
      - Publicity, 1960-1963 (Box 174, Folder 40)
    - Erie
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1967-1973 (Box 174, Folder 41)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1967
        - 1967-1973 (Box 174, Folder 42)
        - 1979 (Box 174)
      - PP Erie County, 1966-1973 (Box 174, Folder 43)
      - Reports, General, 1969-1971 (Box 174, Folder 44)
      - Reports, Members, 1967-1972 (Box 174, Folder 45)
    - Harrisburg
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1950-1970 (Box 174, Folder 46)
      - Affiliation, Correspondence, 1962-1972 (Box 174, Folder 47)
      - Field Trips, 1961-1965 (Box 174, Folder 48)
      - Reports, General, 1968-1969 (Box 174, Folder 49)
      - PP, 1963-1974 (Box 174, Folder 50)
      - Reports, Members, 1963-1970 (Box 174, Folder 51)
      - Publicity from 1962 (empty) (Box 174, Folder 52)
      - Dr. A. F. Guttmacher's Trip, 1962 (Box 174, Folder 53)
      - Pennsylvanians for Freedom of Choice in Family Planning, 1967-1970 (Box 174, Folder 54)
    - Johnstown
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, Documents, 1978-1980 (Box 174, Folder 55)
      - Affiliation, PP of Cambria/Somerset, 1977-1980 (Box 174, Folder 56)
      - PP of Cambria/Somerset, 1977-1979 (Box 174, Folder 57)
      - PP Cambria/Somerset, Reports, Members, 1977 (Box 174, Folder 58)
    - Kittanning PP, 1964-1967 (Box 174, Folder 59)
    - Lancaster
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1950
        - 1950-1974 (Box 174, Folder 60)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 174)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1959
        - 1959-1974 (Box 174, Folder 61)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 174)
      - PP from 1963
        - 1963-1974 (Box 174, Folder 62)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 174)
      - PP of Lancaster, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1979 (Box 174, Folder 63)
      - Field Visits, 1973 (Box 174, Folder 64)
      - Field Trips, 1957-1964 (Box 174, Folder 65)
      - PP, Reports, Clinics, 1958-1970 (Box 174, Folder 66)
      - PP, Reports, General, 1962-1969 (Box 174, Folder 67)
      - PP, Reports, Members from 1962
        - 1962-1970 (Box 174, Folder 68)
        - 1975, 1980 (Box 174)
      - PP, Publicity, 1964 (Box 174, Folder 69)
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1948, 1948-1957 (Box 174, Folder 70)
      - Affiliation, PP Montgomery County, Correspondence, 1957-1960 (Box 174, Folder 71)
      - Field Trips, 1957-1959 (Box 174, Folder 72)
    - Philadelphia
      - PP Association of Southeastern Pennsylvania, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1978 (Box 174, Folder 73)
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1949
        - 1949-1972 (Box 174, Folder 74)
        - 1975, 1978 (Box 174)
      - Affiliation, PP Association, Correspondence from 1958
        - 1958-1974 (Box 174, Folder 75)
        - 1975-1981 (Box 174)
      - PP Association of Southeastern Pennsylvania from 1972
        - 1972-1974 (Box 174, Folder 76)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 174)
      - PP Association, 1969-1971 (Box 174, Folder 77)
      - PP Association, 1968 (Box 175, Folder 1)
      - PP Association, 1966-1967 (Box 175, Folder 2)
      - PP Association, 1965 (Box 175, Folder 3)
      - PP Association, 1964 (Box 175, Folder 4)
      - Council on Sexuality & the Mentally Retarded, Sponsored by PPSP [Planned Parenthood of Southeastern Pennsylvania], undated (Box 175, Folder 5)
      - Field Trips, 1954-1961 (Box 175, Folder 6)
      - PP, Reports, Clinics from 1965
        - 1965-1969 (Box 175, Folder 7)
        - 1977 (Box 175)
      - PP, Reports, General, 1966-1971 (Box 175, Folder 8)
      - PP, Reports, Members from 1962
        - 1962-1971 (Box 175, Folder 9)
        - 1975 (Box 175)
      - PP Association, Publicity Pamphlets, etc., 1960-1972 (Box 175, Folder 10)
    - Pittsburgh
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1949
        - 1949-1974 (Box 175, Folder 11)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 175)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1964
        - 1964-1974 (Box 175, Folder 12)
        - 1975-1981 (Box 175)
      - PP Center of Pittsburgh, Legal (Eve Paul), 1978 (Box 175, Folder 13)
      - PP Center of Pittsburgh, Trip Report, Andy Diaz, 1976 (Box 175, Folder 14)
      - PP Center from 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 175, Folder 15)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 175)
      - PP Center, 1966-1969 (Box 175, Folder 16)
      - PP Center, 1965-1966 (Box 175, Folder 17)
      - PP Center, 1963-1964 (Box 175, Folder 18)
      - PP Center, Patient Information & Instruction, 1968-1970 (Box 175, Folder 19)
      - PP Center, Reports, Clinics, 1957-1964 (Box 175, Folder 20)
      - PP Center, Reports, General from 1957
        - 1956-1969 (Box 175, Folder 21)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 175)
      - Field Trips, 1956-1962 (Box 175, Folder 22)
      - PP Center, Reports, Members from 1963
        - 1963-1971 (Box 175, Folder 23)
        - 1979 (Box 175)
      - PP Center, Publicity, Pamphlets, etc., 1959-1970 (Box 175, Folder 24)
    - Reading
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1953
        - 1953-1973 (Box 175, Folder 25)
        - 1976-1980 (Box 175)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1959
        - 1959-1973 (Box 175, Folder 26)
        - 1976-1980 (Box 175)
      - PP Center Berks County, 1963
        - 1963-1973 (Box 175, Folder 27)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 175)
      - PP Center, Reports, Clinics from 1959
        - 1959-1964 (Box 175, Folder 28)
        - 1975 (Box 175)
      - PP Center, Reports, General, 1962-1964 (Box 175, Folder 29)
      - PP Center, Reports, Members, 1963-1971 (Box 175, Folder 30)
      - PP Center, Publicity, 1955-1969 (Box 175, Folder 31)
      - Field Visits, 1973-1974 (Box 175, Folder 32)
      - Field Trips, 1959-1963 (Box 175, Folder 33)
    - PP State League, Affiliation Situation, State Office, officially closed 1/23/57, 1946-1957 (Box 175, Folder 34)
    - Scranton
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1951
        - 1951-1974 (Box 175, Folder 35)
        - 1977-1980 (Box 175)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1961
        - 1961-1974 (Box 175, Folder 35a)
        - 1977 (Box 175)
      - PP Lackawanna County from 1963
        - 1963-1974 (Box 175, Folder 36)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 175)
      - PP, Reports, General, 1962-1969 (Box 175, Folder 37)
      - PP, Reports, Members, 1963-1970 (Box 175, Folder 38)
      - PP, Publicity, 1960-1969 (Box 175, Folder 39)
      - Field Visits, 1974 (Box 175, Folder 40)
      - Field Trips, 1955-1963 (Box 175, Folder 41)
    - Sharon
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1963-1974 (Box 175, Folder 42)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1963
        - 1963-1974 (Box 175, Folder 43)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 175)
      - PP Committee from 1963
        - 1962-1974 (Box 175, Folder 44)
        - 1975 (Box 175)
      - PP, Reports, Members, 1964-1973 (Box 175, Folder 45)
      - Field Trips, 1963 (Box 175, Folder 46)
    - West Chester
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1967
        - 1967-1973 (Box 175, Folder 47)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 175)
      - Affiliation, PP Chester County from 1967
        - 1967-1974 (Box 175, Folder 48)
        - 1975-1981 (Box 175)
      - PP of Chester County from 1966
        - 1966-1974 (Box 175, Folder 49)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 175)
      - PP Chester County, Reports, General, 1967 (Box 175, Folder 50)
      - PP Chester County, Reports, Members, 1968-1970 (Box 175, Folder 51)
      - PP Chester County, Publicity from 1970 (empty) (Box 175, Folder 52)
    - Wilkes Barre
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1950
        - 1950-1972 (Box 175, Folder 53)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 175)
      - Affiliation, PP Association, Correspondence from 1959
        - 1959-1974 (Box 175, Folder 54)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 175)
      - Field Trips, 1949-1962 (Box 176, Folder 1)
      - PP Association of Luzene County from 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 176, Folder 2)
        - 1976-1979 (Box 176)
      - PP Association, 1963-1969 (Box 176, Folder 3)
      - PP Association, Reports, Clinics, 1956-1965 (Box 176, Folder 4)
      - PP Association, Reports, General, 1965-1966 (Box 176, Folder 5)
      - PP Association, Reports, Members from 1963
        - 1963-1973 (Box 176, Folder 6)
        - 1976, 1980 (Box 176)
    - York
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1954
        - 1956-1973 (Box 176, Folder 7)
        - 1976, 1980 (Box 176)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1952
        - 1952-1974 (Box 176, Folder 8)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 176)
      - PP Central Pennsylvania, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1979 (Box 176, Folder 9)
      - PP Correspondence from 1964
        - 1964-1974 (Box 176, Folder 10)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 176)
      - PP Central Pennsylvania, Chapters, 1976 (Box 176, Folder 11)
      - Field Visit, 1974 (Box 176, Folder 12)
      - Field Trips, 1959-1964 (Box 176, Folder 13)
      - Reports, Clinics, 1964-1965 (Box 176, Folder 14)
      - Reports, General, 1964-1970 (Box 176, Folder 15)
      - PP, Reports, Members, 1962-1971 (Box 176, Folder 16)
      - Publicity, 1958-1964 (Box 176, Folder 17)
    - Mid-Atlantic Region, Reports, Field Trips, 1973 (Box 176, Folder 18)
  - Rhode Island
    - Contacts, 1964-1966 (Box 176, Folder 19)
    - Hospitals, General, 1966-1969 (Box 176, Folder 20)
    - Legal, 1950-1958 (Box 176, Folder 21)
    - Public Health, 1965 (Box 176, Folder 22)
    - Public Welfare, 1965-1967 (Box 176, Folder 23)
    - Schools, General, 1967-1971 (Box 176, Folder 24)
    - Providence
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1951
        - 1951-1973 (Box 176, Folder 25)
        - 1976, 1979 (Box 176)
      - Affiliation, PP Association, Correspondence from 1958
        - 1958-1973 (Box 176, Folder 26)
        - 1975-1981 (Box 176)
      - PP of Rhode Island, Legal (Paul, E.), 1978-1979 (Box 176, Folder 27)
      - PP of Rhode Island from 1971
        - 1971-1974 (Box 176, Folder 28)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 176)
      - Planned Parenthood, 1964-1970 (Box 176, Folder 29)
      - Field Trips, 1953-1964 (Box 176, Folder 30)
      - PP Association, Reports, Clinics, 1961-1969 (Box 176, Folder 31)
      - PP Association, Reports, General, 1960-1967 (Box 176, Folder 32)
      - PP Association, Reports, Members, 1959-1972 (Box 176, Folder 33)
      - Manual for Board Members, 1949-1950 (Box 176, Folder 34)
      - PP Association, Publicity, 1961-1974 (Box 176, Folder 35)
  - South Carolina
    - Anti-Poverty, 1965-1970 (Box 176, Folder 36)
    - Charities, Registration Act, 1973 (Box 176, Folder 37)
    - Contacts from 1964
      - 1964-1973 (Box 176, Folder 38)
      - 1975-1978 (Box 176)
    - Hospitals, 1963-1969 (Box 176, Folder 39)
    - Legal, 1962-1970 (Box 176, Folder 40)
    - Projects, 1969 (Box 176, Folder 41)
    - Public Health, Correspondence from 1963
      - 1964-1974 (Box 176, Folder 42)
      - 1977 (Box 176)
    - Public Health, Family Planning Conference in Columbia, South Carolina, 11/22/1963 (Box 176, Folder 43)
    - Public Welfare, 1962-1968 (Box 176, Folder 44)
    - United Fund, United Community Services, 1963-1974 (Box 176, Folder 45)
    - Schools, General, 1965-1970 (Box 176, Folder 46)
    - State College, 1967 (Box 176, Folder 47)
    - Voorhees College, 1961-1968 (Box 176, Folder 48)
    - Camden
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1962-1970 (Box 176, Folder 49)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence, 1961-1971 (Box 176, Folder 50)
      - PP of Kershaw County, 1970-1971 (Box 176, Folder 51)
      - PP Association Kershaw County, 1963-1971 (Box 176, Folder 52)
      - Field Trips, 1961-1962 (Box 176, Folder 53)
      - PP Committee, Reports, General, 1964-1969 (Box 176, Folder 54)
      - PP Committee, Reports, Members, 1964-1971 (Box 176, Folder 55)
      - PP Committee, Publicity, 1963-1969 (Box 176, Folder 56)
    - Clearwater
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1970
        - 1970-1972 (Box 176, Folder 57)
        - 1975 (Box 176)
      - Affiliation, PP of Aiken County, Correspondence from 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 176, Folder 58)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 176)
      - PP of Aiken County from 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 176, Folder 59)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 176)